Guide to the Richard M. Peabody Gargoyle Magazine collection, circa 1976-2009 MS2040
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Reference files, 1976-1993; MS2040 Series 3
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, A. Salon, Ltd., 1981 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Aberdeen Gallery, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Academy of American Poets, 1985-1986 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Active Culture Exhibits (ACE), undated (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Activities for Downtown Development in the Arts, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Acheron Press, undated (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, American Foundation for AIDS Research, undated (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, American University, 1975-1990 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Andrea Ruggeri Gallery, undated (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Anemone Press, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Arlington Arts Center, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Arlington County Visual and Performing Arts, undated (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Art Barn Association, 1981-1984 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Artscape, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Arts Club of Washington, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Arts Interaction, undated (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Astrea Book Gallery, undated (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Atlantic Center for the Arts, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Bank's World, undated (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Beach and Company Publishers, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Belisarius Book Store, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Belles Lettres: A Review of Books by Women, undated (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Bethesda Ave. Co op, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Bethesda Regional Library, undated (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Bethesda Square, undated (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Black Buzzard Press, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Black Film Review, undated (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Bookstall and W. W. Norton, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Bookworks, undated (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Borders Bookshop, undated (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Botswana, 1987-1988 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Bread and Roses Community Music Center, undated (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Bread Loaf Writers Conference, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Bridge Street Books, undated (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Capitol Hill Arts Workshop, 1986-1990 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Capitol Hill Poetry Group, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Carega Foxley Leach Gallery, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Catholic University of America, undated (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Center for Contemporary Music, undated (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Chapters: A Literary Bookstore, 1980-1987 (Box 36, Folder 41)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Charing Cross Bookshop, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Cherry Valley Edition, undated (Box 36, Folder 43)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Chow Chow Productions, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 44)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Cinque, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 45)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Columbia Historical Society, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 46)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Common Concerns, undated (Box 36, Folder 47)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Community Cafe and Bookstore, undated (Box 36, Folder 48)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Coolidge Auditorium, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 49)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Corcoran School of Art, 1987-1989 (Box 36, Folder 50)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Cosmep South News, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 51)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Daedal Fine Arts, undated (Box 36, Folder 52)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Dance Exchange, undated (Box 36, Folder 53)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Dance Place, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 54)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, D.C. Space, 1984-1991 (Box 36, Folder 55)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Decatur House Press, Limited, undated (Box 36, Folder 56)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Disappear Fear, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 57)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, District Curators, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 58)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Distict Lines, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 59)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, District of Columbia Arts and District Curators, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 60)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, District of Columbia Arts/Pushing the Limits Productions, undated (Box 36, Folder 61)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, District of Columbia Arts Center, undated (Box 36, Folder 62)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, District Columbia Commision on the Arts and Humanities, 1983-1988 (Box 36, Folder 63)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, District of Columbia Community Humanities Council, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 64)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, District of Columbia Public Library, 1978-1986 (Box 36, Folder 65)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, District of Columbia Public Schools, undated (Box 36, Folder 66)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, District of Columbia Wheel Productions, undated (Box 36, Folder 67)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Dolphin Moon Press, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 68)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Dryad Press, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 69)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Dupont Circle Art Galleries, undated (Box 36, Folder 70)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Edes House, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 71)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Ernst Alexander Gallery, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 72)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Fair Oaks Corporate Center, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Fawcett Center for Tomorrow, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Federal Poets, 1986-1988 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Fifteen Minutes Club, undated (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Folger Library, 1976-1989 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Folger Library, 1977-1989 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Foundry Gallery, undated (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Foxely/Leach Gallery, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Franz Bader Gallery, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Fredrick Douglass Creative Arts Center, undated (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Full Moon, undated (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Galileo Press, Ltd., undated (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Gallery International, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Gallery K, 1983-1986 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Gallimauntry Press, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Garlic Press, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Gargoyle MagazinePaycock Press, undated (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Great Ocean Publishers, undated (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, George Mason University, 1978-1988 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, George Mason University,1986-1987. 20a. Arts 20a. Community Promotional Literature, George Washington University: Conf. Workshp, 1981-1986 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, George Washington University, 1984-1990 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Georgetown University, 1980-1989 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Gut Punch Press, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, GYST Press, undated (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Hard Art Gallery, undated (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Herb's Restaurant, undated (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Howard County Literature Society, 1979-1990 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Howard University, 1980-1988 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Images of Cultural Artistry Incorporated, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, International Monetary Fund Visitors Center, 1988-1990 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Indian Cultural Center, 1985-1986 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Industrial Decay Quarterly, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, IPS of American Writing, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Inscape Corporation, 1975-1976 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, The Institute for the Preservation and Study of African American Writing, 1986-1988 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, International Women's Writing Guild, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Intuitiveye Gallery, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Irene Rouse Bookseller, 1980-1984 (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Jarry Performance Studio, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Javarama, nd, undated (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts, nd, undated (Box 37, Folder 41)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Jones Trayer Fitzpatrick Gallery, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 42)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, July 19th Celebration Committee, nd, undated (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Kensington Park Library, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 44)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Kinesis Limited, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 45)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, The King Street Chronicle, nd, undated (Box 37, Folder 46)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Kramerbook and Afterword, 1980-1985 (Box 37, Folder 47)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Lammas Books, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 48)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Lethumplay and Decatur House, nd, undated (Box 37, Folder 49)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Library Of Congress, 1981-1987 (Box 37, Folder 50)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Lightbox Gallery and Studio, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 51)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Living Stage Theater Company, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 52)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Logos and Hysteria, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 53)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Loyola Gallery, nd, undated (Box 37, Folder 54)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, McMillan Taylor Publishers, nd, undated (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Madam's Organ, nd, undated (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Market Five Gallery, nd, undated (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Maryland Arts Council, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Maryland Art Place, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Maryland National Capital Park, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Maryland Poetry and Literary Society, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Maryland Writers Council, nd, undated (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Medium Rare/E.E. Wolensky's Poetry Reading Series, nd, undated (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Meyer Gallery, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Montpellier Cultural Arts Center, 1980-1990 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Montgomery College, 1983-1986 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Montgomery Arts Council, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Mount Saint Mary's College, nd, undated (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Museum of Contemporary Art, nd, undated (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Names Project National Capital Area Chapter, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Nancy Garruba Book Design and Bindery, nd, undated (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, National Abortion Rights Action League, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, National Endowment to the Arts, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Nethers Farm Retreat, nd, undated (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, New Art Examiner, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, New Classroom, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, The New Republic, undated (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, New River, nd, undated (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, New York Mobilization for Justice and Peace in Central America and Southern Africa, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, New Zealand Embassy, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Night Club 9:30, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Northern Virginia Community College, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, OCNWU, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Office of the Cultural Advisor with the Mayor of DC, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Office of the Mayor, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Olshonsky Gallery, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Olsson's Books and Records, undated (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Open Hand Publishing Incorpoated, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Open Studio, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Orion Classics, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Outlaws!, nd, undated (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Pacific Radio, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Pen Syndicated Fiction Project, nd, undated (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Phoebe, The George Mason Review, nd, undated (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Plum Review, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 41)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Poetry Society of America, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 42)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Poets' Audio Center, nd, undated (Box 38, Folder 43)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Poets and Writers Incorporated, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 44)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Politics and Prose, 1980-1990 (Box 38, Folder 45)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Poodles Publishing, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 46)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Positively Prince Street, undated (Box 38, Folder 47)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Publication Party, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 48)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Pushing the Limit, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 49)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Pyrmid Parallels Atlantic, 1987-1990 (Box 38, Folder 50)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Quill and Brush, 1982-1983 (Box 38, Folder 51)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, R.E.A.L foundation, nd, undated (Box 38, Folder 52)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Rebecca Press, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 53)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Reston Community Center, nd, undated (Box 38, Folder 54)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Richard Reitar Fusion, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 55)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Rosebud Awards/The Fifth Annual Washington, D.C. International Film Festival, nd, undated (Box 38, Folder 56)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Salt of the Earth Bookstore and Cultural Center, nd, undated (Box 38, Folder 57)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Sanctuary Theater, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 58)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Satellite Foundation, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 59)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Scop Publications, 1982-1987 (Box 38, Folder 60)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Scripta Humanistica, nd, undated (Box 38, Folder 61)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Second Story Books, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 62)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Second Wind, nd, undated (Box 38, Folder 63)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, 1708 East Main, 1984-1987 (Box 38, Folder 64)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Sibyl child Press, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 65)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Sidwell Friends School, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 66)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Smithsonian National Gallery of Art, 1982-1990 (Box 38, Folder 67)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Smithsonian National Museun of American Art, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 68)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Smithsonian Renwick Gallery, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 69)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Smithsonian General, 1982-1989 (Box 38, Folder 70)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Source Theater's Washington, nd, undated (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Soya Designs, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Square Gallery, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Station to Station Writers Collective, 1984-1987 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, St. John's Coffee House: United Methodist Church, undated (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Strathmore Hall Arts Center, 1987-1989 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Sun and Moon Press, 1983-1987 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Synergy Dance and Movement Center, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Takoma Cafe, 1984-1988 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Takoma Park Library, 1983-1985 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Takoma Traders, nd, undated (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Three Continent Press, 1979-1983 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, TideWaters Publishers, nd, undated (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Trenton Street Shop, nd, undated (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, 20th Century Gallery, nd, undated (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Union Temple Baptist Church, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, United Nations, nd, undated (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, University of Baltimore, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, University of Maryland, 1984-1988 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Virginia Center for the Creative Arts, nd, undated (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Walden Books, nd, undated (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Washington Artists Congress, 1977-1978 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Washington County, Maryland Arts Council, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Washington D.C. Affiliate of the National Federation of Press Woman, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Washington D.C. Book Fair, 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Washington Expatriates Press, nd, undated (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Washingtonian, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Washington Independant Writers, 1984-1990 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Washington International School, nd, undated (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Washington Organizing Committee of the National Writers Union, undated (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Washington Performing Arts Society, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, The Washington Post, nd, undated (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Washington Post, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Washington Project for the Arts, 1978-1988 (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Washington Resources Incorporated, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Washington Reviews, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, The Washington Show, nd, undated (Box 39, Folder 37)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Washington School, 1983-1987 (Box 39, Folder 38)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Washington Women's Art Center, 1978-1982 (Box 39, Folder 39)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Washington Writers Publishing House, 1986-1987 (Box 39, Folder 40)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Washington Writers Union, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 41)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Watershed Foundation, nd, undated (Box 39, Folder 42)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, WHACO, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 43)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, WHFS 102.3 FM Pipeline, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 44)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, White Ewe Press, 1982-1983 (Box 39, Folder 45)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Willow Street Gallery, nd, undated (Box 39, Folder 46)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Wineberry Press, undated (Box 39, Folder 47)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, Woodbine House, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 48)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, WordWorks, nd, undated (Box 39, Folder 49)
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, World Bank, 1985-1988 (Box 39, Folder 50)